...were made by the fbi...york police today in a massive mob
bust several infinite mafia families along the east coast were involved here's what we know the
fbi erected more than forty people allegedly involved in organized crime they've
been charged with weapons trafficking extortion illegal gambling
healthcare and credit card fraud assault and other offenses members of the
...gambino lucchese capi
and bonanno mafia families are involved investigators say they allegedly ran
a huge business called the east coast enterprise and there are some interesting
...some of those charged that...now merge among them rooster tony the
...muscle...boy tony the cripple nikki the
...mustache pat tugboat.
At the kid and big vinnie right now we know nearly all of the
...charged are in custody.